// Hardcoding Questions using Object Literals
const STORE = {
    questions : [
        {
        question : "What is one basis point equivalent to in terms of pricing structure?",
        options : [
            "1%",
            "0.1%",
            "0.01%",
            "0.001%"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "0.1%"
        },
        {
        question : "What is PCI-Compliance?",
        options : [
            "Terminal Software",
            "Data and Network Safety Criteria for Merchants",
            "Post Credit Inquiry Compliance",
            "Personal Computer Interface Compliance"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Data and Network Safety Criteria for Merchants"
        },
        {
        question : "What is MID short for?",
        options : [
            "Money Initialization Day",
            "Merchant Identification",
            "Merchant Infrastructure Duties",
            "Max Increment Data"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Merchant Identification"
        },
        {
        question : "What pricing model passes all fees onto the customer?",
        options : [
            "Cash Discounting",
            "Surcharging",
            "Interchange Plus",
            "Flat Rate"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Cash Discounting"
        },
        {
        question : "What pricing model passes some fees onto the customer?",
        options : [
            "Cash Discounting",
            "Interchange Plus",
            "Flat Rate",
            "Surcharging"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Surcharging"
        },
        {
        question : "What pricing model is most common?",
        options : [
            "Surcharging",
            "Flat Rate",
            "Cash Discounting",
            "Interchange Plus"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Interchange Plus"
        },
        {
        question : "If you have a month volume of $10000 and a profit margin of 15BPs how much are you making?",
        options : [
            "$1500",
            "$150",
            "$15",
            "$1.50"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "$15"
        },
        {
        question : "What is it called when a merchant stops processing?",
        options : [
            "Drop out",
            "Deconversion",
            "Cancellation",
            "Merchant Request"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Deconversion"
        },
        {
        question : "What is the most common residual split in the industry?",
        options : [
            "20%",
            "30%",
            "40%",
            "50%"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "40%"
        },
        {
        question : "How many new merchants does the average MS Sales Person Sign Monthly?",
        options : [
            "3",
            "5",
            "9",
            "11"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "9"
        },
    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    currentScore: 0
}